## Heaven Saenz

1155 Hassinger St. Apt 402 Honolulu, HI 96822 808-799-5888

# **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

Motivated and self-taught front-end web developer eager to join a team where I can utilize my technical and creative skills to contribute to the growth and success of the company. I am an open learner and welcome all challenges to expand my knowledge in all areas of web development.

WEB: Heavenlee.xyz

EMAIL: heavenlee@me.com

#### **SKILLS**

Tools: Languages:

Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator CSS3, HTML5, JavaScript, PHP Sublime Text, Xcode, Terminal, Git Jquery Wordpress, Bootstrap

# Personal Project - <a href="http://heavenlee.xyz">http://heavenlee.xyz</a>

My own personal website which utilizes the Bootstrap framework. The features include responsive web design to provide the best viewing experience on all devices.

#### RELEVANT COURSEWORK

Udemy - Rob Percival: The Complete Web Developer Course
Team Treehouse - Front End Web Development
Leeward Community College - NetPrep Web Development Course - 3 credits

#### **EDUCATION**

Paul Mitchell the School Honolulu, Kaimuki, HI — Cosmetology, 2014-2015

Leeward Community College, Pearl City, HI — Digital Media Production, 2009 - 2012

Associates of Science in Digital Media Production | Certificate of Competence in Motion Graphics

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

Stylist, Supercuts; Waialae, HI — September 2015 - Present

Provided in-depth consultations with clients to ensure optimal results. Opening/closing store procedures.

## Assistant, Salon Andre; Mililani, HI — March 2015 - August 2015 (Closed)

Assisted salon owner with social media and marketing. Greeted guest promptly and served refreshments to clients. Recorded client information using salon software. Handled multiple clients with ease and patience.